{"quizTitle":"How much do you know about COVID-19? Letâ€™s find out!","quizSynopsis":"With this deadly pandemic affecting thousands of people and taking hundreds of lives every day across the globe, it becomes all the more important to know most about it.Because, the more you know, the easier it gets to tackle it.","questions":[{"question":"What is the best way to clean your hands?","option_4":"Soil","correctAnswer":"1","questionType":"text","answerSelectionType":"single","messageForCorrectAnswer":"Correct answer. Good job.","messageForIncorrectAnswer":"Incorrect answer. Please try again.","point":10,"answers":["Soap and Water","Alcohol based Sanitizer","Water"]},{"question":"How does Coronavirus spread?","correctAnswer":"3","questionType":"text","answerSelectionType":"single","messageForCorrectAnswer":"Correct answer. Good job.","messageForIncorrectAnswer":"Incorrect answer. Please try again.","point":10,"answers":["Eating chicken","Drinking dirty water","Getting in contact of an infected person"]},{"question":"Where was the first case of coronavirus reported?","option_4":"Rome","correctAnswer":"1","questionType":"text","answerSelectionType":"single","messageForCorrectAnswer":"Correct answer. Good job.","messageForIncorrectAnswer":"Incorrect answer. Please try again.","point":10,"answers":["Wuhan","Shanghai","Singapore"]},{"question":"What is the minimum distance one should maintain from another to stay safe?","option_4":"Not needed","correctAnswer":"1","questionType":"text","answerSelectionType":"single","messageForCorrectAnswer":"Correct answer. Good job.","messageForIncorrectAnswer":"Incorrect answer. Please try again.","point":10,"answers":["3feet","5feet","1feet"]},{"question":"Where is the first human trial of a coronavirus vaccine taking place?","correctAnswer":"2","questionType":"text","answerSelectionType":"single","messageForCorrectAnswer":"Correct answer. Good job.","messageForIncorrectAnswer":"Incorrect answer. Please try again.","point":10,"answers":["UK","USA","China"]},{"question":"Which is the first Indian company to get Covid-19 test kits validated?","correctAnswer":"2","questionType":"text","answerSelectionType":"single","messageForCorrectAnswer":"Correct answer. Good job.","messageForIncorrectAnswer":"Incorrect answer. Please try again.","point":10,"answers":["MedLab","MyLab","MyDala"]},{"question":"Which of these is a symptom of Covid-19?","correctAnswer":"3","questionType":"text","answerSelectionType":"single","messageForCorrectAnswer":"Correct answer. Good job.","messageForIncorrectAnswer":"Incorrect answer. Please try again.","point":10,"answers":["Eczema","Insomnia","Dry Cough"]},{"question":"How many coronavirus cases were reported on the cruise ship Diamond Princess?","correctAnswer":"1","questionType":"text","answerSelectionType":"single","messageForCorrectAnswer":"Correct answer. Good job.","messageForIncorrectAnswer":"Incorrect answer. Please try again.","point":10,"answers":[700,900,1200]},{"question":"What age was the oldest person to recover from coronavirus?","correctAnswer":"1","questionType":"text","answerSelectionType":"single","messageForCorrectAnswer":"Correct answer. Good job.","messageForIncorrectAnswer":"Incorrect answer. Please try again.","point":10,"answers":[103,95,100]},{"question":"Where was the first case of coronavirus reported in India?","correctAnswer":"2","questionType":"text","answerSelectionType":"single","messageForCorrectAnswer":"Correct answer. Good job.","messageForIncorrectAnswer":"Incorrect answer. Please try again.","point":10,"answers":["Karnataka","Kerala","Uttar Pradesh"]},{"question":"Which Virus causes Covid-19?","correctAnswer":"1","questionType":"text","answerSelectionType":"single","messageForCorrectAnswer":"Correct answer. Good job.","messageForIncorrectAnswer":"Incorrect answer. Please try again.","point":10,"answers":["SARS-CoV2","SARS-CoV","MERS-CoV"]},{"question":"Which country is following \"Drive Through Testing\"?","correctAnswer":"3","questionType":"text","answerSelectionType":"single","messageForCorrectAnswer":"Correct answer. Good job.","messageForIncorrectAnswer":"Incorrect answer. Please try again.","point":10,"answers":["USA","China","South Korea"]},{"question":"When should you use face mask?","correctAnswer":"1","questionType":"text","answerSelectionType":"single","messageForCorrectAnswer":"Correct answer. Good job.","messageForIncorrectAnswer":"Incorrect answer. Please try again.","point":10,"answers":["When you are sick","While going out","All the time"]},{"question":"For how long should you wash your hands to be safe?","correctAnswer":"2","questionType":"text","answerSelectionType":"single","messageForCorrectAnswer":"Correct answer. Good job.","messageForIncorrectAnswer":"Incorrect answer. Please try again.","point":10,"answers":["30 seconds","20 seconds","10 seconds"]},{"question":"You should go out only to","correctAnswer":"1","questionType":"text","answerSelectionType":"single","messageForCorrectAnswer":"Correct answer. Good job.","messageForIncorrectAnswer":"Incorrect answer. Please try again.","point":10,"answers":["Buy groceries","Meet friends","Play cricket"]},{"question":"Which of these statements is true?","option_4":3,"correctAnswer":"text","questionPic":"single","answerSelectionType":"Correct answer. Good job.","messageForCorrectAnswer":"Incorrect answer. Please try again.","explanation":10,"answers":["Drinking Cow urine builds immunity against Covid19","Hot water bath prevents you from catching Covid-19","Covid-19 spreads through droplets generated by cough or sneeze of the infected person"]},{"question":"Spraying alcohol or chlorine over your body kills the Coronavirus.","correctAnswer":"2","questionType":"text","answerSelectionType":"single","messageForCorrectAnswer":"Correct answer. Good job.","messageForIncorrectAnswer":"Incorrect answer. Please try again.","point":10,"answers":["Yes","No","Maybe"]},{"question":"Vaccines against pneumonia protects you against the Coronavirus.","correctAnswer":"2","questionType":"text","answerSelectionType":"single","messageForCorrectAnswer":"Correct answer. Good job.","messageForIncorrectAnswer":"Incorrect answer. Please try again.","point":10,"answers":["Yes","No","Maybe"]},{"question":"How can you prevent getting infected with the Coronavirus?","correctAnswer":"1","questionType":"text","answerSelectionType":"single","messageForCorrectAnswer":"Correct answer. Good job.","messageForIncorrectAnswer":"Incorrect answer. Please try again.","point":10,"answers":["Staying away from infected person","Eating garlic","Rinsing your nose with saline"]},{"question":"Eating Garlic can help prevent infection with the Coronavirus.","correctAnswer":"2","questionType":"text","answerSelectionType":"single","messageForCorrectAnswer":"Correct answer. Good job.","messageForIncorrectAnswer":"Incorrect answer. Please try again.","point":10,"answers":["Yes","No","Maybe"]},{"question":"Coronavirus only affects older people.","correctAnswer":"3","questionType":"text","answerSelectionType":"single","messageForCorrectAnswer":"Correct answer. Good job.","messageForIncorrectAnswer":"Incorrect answer. Please try again.","point":10,"answers":["Yes, It only affects people above 60 years","Yes, It only affects older people with pre-existing medical conditions","No, People of all ages can be infected"]},{"question":"Are antibiotics effective in preventing and treating the Coronavirus?","correctAnswer":"2","questionType":"text","answerSelectionType":"single","messageForCorrectAnswer":"Correct answer. Good job.","messageForIncorrectAnswer":"Incorrect answer. Please try again.","point":10,"answers":["Yes, antibiotics prevent and treat Coronavirus","No, antibiotics do not work against viruses","Effective in some cases"]},{"question":"Covid-19 can be transmitted in hot and humid areas.","correctAnswer":"1","questionType":"text","answerSelectionType":"single","messageForCorrectAnswer":"Correct answer. Good job.","messageForIncorrectAnswer":"Incorrect answer. Please try again.","point":10,"answers":["Yes","No","Maybe"]},{"question":"Can I catch the coronavirus disease (COVID-19) from my pet?","correctAnswer":"2","questionType":"text","answerSelectionType":"single","messageForCorrectAnswer":"Correct answer. Good job.","messageForIncorrectAnswer":"Incorrect answer. Please try again.","point":10,"answers":["Yes","No","Maybe"]},{"question":"The Coronavirus can be transmitted through mosquito bites.","correctAnswer":"2","questionType":"text","answerSelectionType":"single","messageForCorrectAnswer":"Correct answer. Good job.","messageForIncorrectAnswer":"Incorrect answer. Please try again.","point":10,"answers":["Yes","No","Maybe"]},{"question":"Are hand dryers effective in killing the new coronavirus?","correctAnswer":"2","questionType":"text","answerSelectionType":"single","messageForCorrectAnswer":"Correct answer. Good job.","messageForIncorrectAnswer":"Incorrect answer. Please try again.","point":10,"answers":["Yes","No","Maybe"]},{"question":"Can you catch the Coronavirus and show no symptoms?","correctAnswer":"1","questionType":"text","answerSelectionType":"single","messageForCorrectAnswer":"Correct answer. Good job.","messageForIncorrectAnswer":"Incorrect answer. Please try again.","point":10,"answers":["Yes, because it has 5 days incubation period","No, symptoms are visible from day 1","Maybe"]},{"question":"Can you catch the Coronavirus for the second time?","correctAnswer":"3","questionType":"text","answerSelectionType":"single","messageForCorrectAnswer":"Correct answer. Good job.","messageForIncorrectAnswer":"Incorrect answer. Please try again.","point":10,"answers":["You can get infected again","You only get infected once","Depends on how long the immunity of the patient lasts"]},{"question":"How long can the Cornonavirus survive on surfaces?","correctAnswer":"3","questionType":"text","answerSelectionType":"single","messageForCorrectAnswer":"Correct answer. Good job.","messageForIncorrectAnswer":"Incorrect answer. Please try again.","point":10,"answers":["It doesn't stick to surfaces","Surfaces remain infected always","Depends on the surface material and the amount of virus present"]},{"question":"How long can the Cornonavirus survive on copper?","correctAnswer":"2","questionType":"text","answerSelectionType":"single","messageForCorrectAnswer":"Correct answer. Good job.","messageForIncorrectAnswer":"Incorrect answer. Please try again.","point":10,"answers":["Up to 5hrs","Up to 4hrs","Up to 3hrs"]},{"question":"How long can the Cornonavirus survive on cardboard?","correctAnswer":"1","questionType":"text","answerSelectionType":"single","messageForCorrectAnswer":"Correct answer. Good job.","messageForIncorrectAnswer":"Incorrect answer. Please try again.","point":10,"answers":["Up to 24hrs","Up to 20hrs","Up to 15hrs"]},{"question":"How long can the Cornonavirus survive on plastic?","correctAnswer":"1","questionType":"text","answerSelectionType":"single","messageForCorrectAnswer":"Correct answer. Good job.","messageForIncorrectAnswer":"Incorrect answer. Please try again.","point":10,"answers":["Up to 3 days","Up to 5 days","Up to 7 days"]},{"question":"How long can the Cornonavirus survive on stainless steel?","correctAnswer":"3","questionType":"text","answerSelectionType":"single","messageForCorrectAnswer":"Correct answer. Good job.","messageForIncorrectAnswer":"Incorrect answer. Please try again.","point":10,"answers":["Up to 7 days","Up to 5 days","Up to 3 days"]},{"question":"How long can the Cornonavirus survive in air?","correctAnswer":"3","questionType":"text","answerSelectionType":"single","messageForCorrectAnswer":"Correct answer. Good job.","messageForIncorrectAnswer":"Incorrect answer. Please try again.","point":10,"answers":["Up to 5hrs","Up to 4hrs","Up to 3hrs"]}]}